mgmmiragevacations.com 2005-12-14

# MGM MIRAGE Vacations - Las Vegas vacation travel packages Las Vegas attractions MGM Grand, Bellagio, New York-New York, Treasure Island, Mirage Hotel & Casino, Las Vegas strip hotels special deal wedding package golf package Las Vegas air/hotel package

Introduction  
MGM MIRAGE Vacations believes in protecting your privacy. We provide this privacy policy to help you better understand the ways in which your personal information is gathered from our [MGM MIRAGE Vacations website](http://www.mgmmiragevacations.com/) and utilized. Be assured that the information you provide to us via the mgmmiragevacation.com site is confidential. We do not rent or sell your personal information to any third party company or agency without your authorization.

The Mark Travel Corporation and its affiliated technology and marketing agencies, and travel agency distributors, gather, store, and process the information from the [MGM MIRAGE Vacations website](http://www.mgmmiragevacations.com/). They help MGM MIRAGE Vacations use customer information to create and distribute products, specials, promotions, and website features for our customers.

Information MGM MIRAGE Vacations Collects  
MGM MIRAGE Vacations collects your information when you perform the following actions on our website:

  * Request to receive promotional/informational emails via the Guest Book
  * Book reservations using the MGM MIRAGE Vacations online booking form
  * Submit customer service requests and/or comments using the online forms
  * Forward postcards or our web page to friends

The types of information collected includes: | 

  * Customer and passenger names
  * Mailing address
  * Email address
  * Telephone number

| 

  * Age of traveler(s)
  * Gender of traveler(s)
  * Travel habits
  * Reservation numberCredit/debit card information

---|---  
  
How Your Information Is Used  
Our website hosts a Guest Book, where you may subscribe to receive our **_"Priority News and Notes"_** service. You will be among the first to receive up-to-the-minute details on limited time price reductions, special value inclusions, and product developments. This service provides you the best opportunity to book our vacation specials and take advantage of limited inventory at reduced prices. You may unsubscribe from the email list at any time by accessing the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any email or by visiting the [unsubscribe page](http://www.mgmmiragevacations.com//unsub.asp) on our website.

The information you supply when booking a vacation online is used to process and complete your reservation. MGM MIRAGE Vacations does not share your information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to process your vacation (for example, credit card authorizations). Information submitted while booking is not used to subscribe you to the **_"Priority News and Notes"_**.

The information you supply when submitting a Customer Service request is used to assist you with your request. It may also be used to help MGM MIRAGE Vacations review and improve its products, promotions, and customer service.

The information you supply when submitting suggestions or comments via the Customer Service or Comments links are used to reply to your comment. Your information may also be forwarded on to the relevant product teams or customer service teams to further process your comment or to help improve MGM MIRAGE Vacations product, promotions, and customer service.

The information you supply when sending a post card or our web page to a friend is used to forward the relevant email or web page information. MGM MIRAGE Vacations will not send additional emails or mailings to your friend. Your friend must subscribe to **_"Priority News and Notes"_** in order to receive emails from MGM MIRAGE Vacations directly. 

Information collected through any of the methods listed above may be used by MGM MIRAGE Vacations to improve products, processes and customer service. MGM MIRAGE Vacations may also use any of the information to create customer mailing lists and may occasionally send promotional pieces or other mailings to our customers. Mailing lists compiled from the information you provide is be used only by MGM MIRAGE Vacations for its own marketing and promotional efforts, and will not be sold or shared with any third parties.

MGM MIRAGE Vacations may also use non-identifying or aggregate information to improve our website, track promotional success, and/or to share website usage information with our hotel, airline or other business partners. This information may include the quantity of website pages viewed, quantity of visitors, length of time spent visiting our site, quantity of unique visitors, browser types, number of visits by each visitor, most requested pages, and more. Some of this information is shared with our business partners including aggregate numbers such as particular page views during a specified time frame. However, no personally identifiable information about you is shared with third parties.

MGM MIRAGE Vacations use of IP Addresses and Cookies  
Cookies are tiny files that are placed on the hard drive of your computer as you visit sites on the Internet. Cookies do not extract private or personal information from your computer. MGM MIRAGE Vacations uses cookies to track visitors to our web site. MGM MIRAGE Vacations gathers the number of unique visitors as well as the number of page views each visitor makes. The information is used for promotional and marketing purposes only and in the compilation of web usage reports. The reports generated do not recognize any information specific to your location, or anything specific to your individual machine. We do not utilize cookies to save your credit card number. You must type your credit card number in each time you purchase travel with us online. The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether.

MGM MIRAGE Vacations Commitment to Information Security  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, there are appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. We utilize SSL (Secure Socket Layers) to encrypt and protect your personal information and understand that your security is vital.

MGM MIRAGE Vacations Commitment to Child Privacy  
Protecting the privacy of children is crucial to MGM MIRAGE Vacations. MGM MIRAGE Vacations does not collect or maintain information from our website from those known to be under 13 years of age. No part of our website is designed to attract anyone younger than 13 years of age. While booking a reservation, the ages of children traveling with are collected so appropriate hotel room and prices are selected. The lowest age range specified on the guest book sign up form is "under 18".

How to Access or Update Your Information  
You may access the personal information you submitted while booking your reservation online by retrieving your reservation using your reservation number and password. Please be certain to use reasonable precautions to protect your password by not sharing it with others or storing it where others can view it.

Information submitted through any of the online methods described above, may be used to create customer mailing lists. MGM MIRAGE Vacations occasionally sends our customers promotional pieces or other mailings. Mailing lists compiled from the information you provide will be used only by MGM MIRAGE Vacations for its own marketing and promotional efforts, and will not be sold or shared with any third parties.

Notification of Changes to MGM MIRAGE Vacations Information-Use Policies  
If at some future date, MGM MIRAGE Vacations determines that it will change the manner in which it uses the information it collects on the website, you will be notified at least 30 days prior to MGM MIRAGE Vacations making the change. At that point, you have the option of choosing to continue or discontinue being a member of the MGM MIRAGE Vacations database receiving emails. Information collected prior to any information-use changes would be managed according to the Privacy Policy in place at the time it was collected. Only new information collected online would be subject to any new information-use policies.

How to Contact MGM MIRAGE Vacations  
If you have questions or comments regarding the MGM MIRAGE Vacations privacy policy, please contact MGM MIRAGE Vacations via our online [Customer Service](http://www.mgmmiragevacations.com//custsvc.asp).
